[{"answer": "No, really not.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Anything massively surprising there?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "That she had a massive heart attack of some sort and then drowned?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know if he'll get arrested or when he'll get arrested.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Is the guy that shot this young boy going to get arrested?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I'm going to come back to the campaign in just a moment.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "I'm doing well, how are you?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, my view is that the local district attorney is doing exactly the right thing.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, there are three answers.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "And secondly, at what point politically does it become damaging to you to continue to stay in the race if the current rate of delegate gains and state wins by Mitt Romney continues at the pace that it's now happening?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, no matter what words go back and forth between us, Callista and I were delighted to be at the Kennedy Center Honors when he was honored.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Newt Gingrich, how do you respond to the charge from one of Hollywood's great actors that you are a hypocrite?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "I really think the use of racism by Democrats is just as bad as the use of racism by Republicans, and I really think it's wrong to use racial references like that, period.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Did you really feel offended by Robert De Niro or was it just a chance to whack a Democrat?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No, I actually -- I actually think --", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "That the kind of vicious, nasty things he said are OK?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No, but it's interesting you mention Bill Maher because he wrote a very good piece in \"The New York Times\" today precisely about America's collective sense of humor failure.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "-- vicious, nasty things in the left?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, it applies both ways.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Because everyone is saying that to him about you, but the same applies to you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Are they going to tell Sanchez, move over, because now we have to give Tebow and the wildcat formation time to practice?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, I tell you, the way the Jets have played recently, they need the Good Lord on their side.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "He is not Broadway Joe, is he?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Oh, hey, this young man, I've had had the pleasure of watching him work since he started college in Florida.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "So you don't think it will be too much temptation for him coming to a city like New York?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, it's part of the game when you don't intentionally want to maim someone, when you don't intentionally say, we need to knock this guy out and you're going to get a bonus if he's carried off the field or you're going to get a different bonus if he has to leave the game.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "I mean isn't that part of the game?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Twenty --", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "How long have you two been married?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "And you're still holding hands.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Seven?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "No, no, no, we're all right.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Is this because you're nervous or you still love each other?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I mean I can't imagine.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Was it true?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes, exactly.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Who's going to be your co-host?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I feel so bad for Mark Sanchez.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Are you excited about this?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Well, I tell you, I think -- I used to do sports years ago and I love sports.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "This is not good news, is it?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I saw Andrea Mitchell on that other cable station.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "And I'm sure that, you know, if you were still doing the news broadcast and you feel the same way I do, which is, this whole thing of \"Stand Your Ground,\" allowing someone to just apparently follow after this unarmed kid and kill him and not even be arrested in America today?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Unbelievable.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Yes, but to me, what bothers me more is, how does the Florida Supreme Court allow that law?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "But I just think it's crazy, crazy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "And you got the scoop?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "That was President Nixon for you.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Isn't that strange?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "It's -- I mean, I really believe -- I mean, Reagan -- Ronald Reagan believed in the 11th amendment.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "It's vicious, isn't it?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120322pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Will you come back?", "qSentId": 679}]